Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Departmental / program affairs, 1970 - 1985; F-23-3; 1.19 m of textual records
  - Kinesiology, 1971 - 1985; F-23-3-7; 25 cm of textual records
    - General correspondence, 1971 - 1972; F-23-3-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - General correspondence, 1971 - 1976; F-23-3-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - General correspondence, 1973 - 1975; F-23-3-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - General correspondence, 1977 - 1980; F-23-3-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - General correspondence, 1981 - 1982; F-23-3-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - General correspondence, 1982 - 1983; F-23-3-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - General correspondence, 1984 - 1985; F-23-3-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - Departmental review 1/3, 1973; F-23-3-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - Departmental review 2/3, 1973; F-23-3-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - Departmental review 3/3, 1973; F-23-3-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - Departmental review, 1973 - 1976; F-23-3-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-14)
    - Departmental governance, 1978; F-23-3-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Departmental meetings, 1982 - 1984; F-23-3-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Departmental tenure committee, 1972; F-23-3-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Departmental tenure committee, 1973 - 1984; F-23-3-7-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Certificate program in health fitness, 1978; F-23-3-7-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Curriculum, 1973 - 1975; F-23-3-7-0-17 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Distance Education, 1978 - 1983; F-23-3-7-0-18 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Environmental physiology unit, 1977 - 1981; F-23-3-7-0-19 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Conference - The Female Athlete, 1979 - 1980; F-23-3-7-0-20 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Institute for Human Performance, 1979 - 1982; F-23-3-7-0-21 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Institute for Human Performance, 1981 - 1982; F-23-3-7-0-22 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Institute for Human Performance, 1983; F-23-3-7-0-23 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
    - Joint program with Education, 1981 - 1984; F-23-3-7-0-24 (Archival box - standard 23-15)
  - Natural Resource Management, 1979 - 1983; F-23-3-8; 8 cm of textual records
    - General correspondence, 1982 - 1983; F-23-3-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
    - Curriculum Proposal - Executive committee, 1979 - 1981; F-23-3-8-0-2
  - Women's Studies, 1976 - 1983; F-23-3-9; 4 cm of textual records
    - General correspondence, 1976; F-23-3-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
    - General correspondence, 1977 - 1980; F-23-3-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
    - General correspondence, 1981 - 1983; F-23-3-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
  - Africa/Middle East Studies program, 1972 - 1986; F-23-3-10; 25 cm of textual records
    - AME Studies - Steering Committee minutes, 1981; F-23-3-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - courses, 1972 - 1978; F-23-3-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - history of course offerings, 1972 - 1981; F-23-3-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - content courses, 1972 - 1983; F-23-3-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - progress report, January 1973; F-23-3-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - course offerings, 1975 - 1979; F-23-3-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - advertising, 1975 - 1986; F-23-3-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - correspondence, 1975 - 1986; F-23-3-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - Swahili course, 1976 - 1978; F-23-3-10-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - Major proposal, 1976 - 1979; F-23-3-10-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - Joint Major proposal, 1977 - 1978; F-23-3-10-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - posters, 1978 - 1983; F-23-3-10-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - proposal for a Minor in Africa / Middle East Studies, 1980; F-23-3-10-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-39)
    - AME Studies - new course proposals, May 1980; F-23-3-10-0-14 (Archival box - small 23-40)
    - History of course enrollment (SC 206), 1981 - 1985; F-23-3-10-0-15 (Archival box - small 23-40)
    - PACUP (Pesident's Advisory Committe on University Priorities, 1984; F-23-3-10-0-16 (Archival box - small 23-40)
    - AME 001-3 An Introduction to Africa and the Middle East, 1979 - 1980; F-23-3-10-0-17 (Archival box - small 23-40)
    - AME 110-3 An Introduction to Modern Standard Arabic I, 1981 - 1982; F-23-3-10-0-18 (Archival box - small 23-40)
    - AME 112-3 An Introduction to Modern Standard Arabic II, 1981 - 1985; F-23-3-10-0-19 (Archival box - small 23-40)
    - AME 401-4, 401-5 Studies in Africa, 1979 - 1985; F-23-3-10-0-20 (Archival box - small 23-40)
    - AME 402-4, 402-5 Studies in the Middle East, 1979 - 1985; F-23-3-10-0-21 (Archival box - small 23-40)
    - Swahili 101, 102 - Introductory Swahili, 1972 - 1975; F-23-3-10-0-22 (Archival box - small 23-40)
- Administrative committees, 1974 - 1985; F-23-4; 26 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to committees concerned with the administration and the evaluation of the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies (FIDS). The Dean's Advisory Committee consisted of the FIDS departmental chairs and program directors. FIDS was reviewed by the University Review Committee and the Presidential Advisory Committee on University Priorities; various Senate committees liaised with FIDS in matters of curriculum and student representation; and the Dean of FIDS was a key member of university committees concerned with computing policy because of the Department of Computing Science within FIDS. Series includes agendas, minutes, reports, and working papers.
  - Dean's Advisory Committee - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1977 - 1978; F-23-4-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1977 - 1981; F-23-4-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1982; F-23-4-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee - General Correspondence, 1982; F-23-4-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1983 - 1984; F-23-4-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
  - Dean's Advisory Committee - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1984 - 1985; F-23-4-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-16)
  - University Review Committee - Information on FIDS prgms., 1977; F-23-4-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Africa/Middle East Studies, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Canadian Studies Program, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Centre for the Arts, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Communications Studies department, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Computing Science program, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Criminology Department, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - General Studies, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Kinesiology Department, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Latin American Studies, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - University Review Committee - Women's Studies, 1977; F-23-4-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - SFU Computing Policy Committee, 1982 - 1983; F-23-4-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - SFU Computing Policy Committee, 1983 - 1984; F-23-4-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - SFU Computing Policy Committee, 1984 - 1985; F-23-4-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - SFU Computing Planning Task Force Committee, 1980 - 1984; F-23-4-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - Computing Science Department/Computer Centre Liaison Committee, 1981 - 1983; F-23-4-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 23-17)
  - President's Advisory Committee on University Priorities (PACUP), 1984; F-23-4-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
  - PACUP - Review of FIDS, 1984; F-23-4-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
  - Senate Committee on Student Representation, 1979 - 1981; F-23-4-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
  - Senate Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1974 - 1979; F-23-4-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
  - Senate Task Force on Organization of Faculties, 1978 - 1981; F-23-4-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
- Curriculum and instruction, 1971 - 1985; F-23-5; 2.08 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the development of courses in the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies, the operation of undergraduate and graduate programs, and the awarding of degrees. Series includes committee agendas and minutes, program proposals, course descriptions, and other documents.
  - Undergraduate Curriculum Committee, 1972 - 1985; F-23-5-1; 1.03 m of textual records
    Series consists of records relating to the development and delivery of courses to undergraduate students. The UGCC (also known as FISC) was composed of one faculty member from each department or program within the Faculty, the Dean, and three students. Series includes agendas, minutes, correspondence, working papers and other documents.
    - UGCC - Agendas, 1972 - 1982; F-23-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-12: Kinesiology 142-3 - Change of Vector, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-168.1 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Agenda items summary, 1973 - 1981; F-23-5-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
    - UGCC - Minutes, 1972 - 1978; F-23-5-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
    - UGCC - Minutes, 1978 - 1982; F-23-5-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
    - UGCC - Agenda and minutes, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
    - UGCC - Agenda and minutes, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-18)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-23: Latin American Studies Curriculum Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Agenda and minutes, 1982 - 1984; F-23-5-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-19)
    - UGCC - Papers 1972-01 to 1973-01, 1972 - 1973; F-23-5-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-19)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-22: Women's Studies Curriculum Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Papers 1973-01 to 1973-18, F-23-5-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-19)
    - UGCC - Papers 1974-01 to 1974-18 1/2, F-23-5-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-19)
    - UGCC - Papers 1974-01 to 1974-18 2/2, F-23-5-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-19)
    - UGCC - Papers 1975-01 to 1975-14, F-23-5-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-19)
    - UGCC - Papers 1976-01 to 1976-17, F-23-5-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-19)
    - UGCC - Papers 1976-18 to 1976-39, F-23-5-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-20)
    - UGCC - Papers 1977-01 to 1977-7, 1976; F-23-5-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-20)
    - UGCC - Papers 1977-01 to 1977-13, 1976; F-23-5-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-20)
    - UGCC - Papers 1977-08 to 1976-31, F-23-5-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 23-20)
    - UGCC - Papers 1977-14 to 1977-39, 1976; F-23-5-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 23-20)
    - UGCC - Papers 1977-32 to 1977-42, F-23-5-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 23-20)
    - UGCC - Papers 1978-01 to 1978-28, F-23-5-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 23-21)
    - UGCC - Papers 1978-29 to 1979-14, 1978 - 1979; F-23-5-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 23-21)
    - UGCC - Papers 1979-15 to 1980-12, 1979 - 1980; F-23-5-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 23-21)
    - UGCC - Papers 1980-13 to 1980-25, F-23-5-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 23-21)
    - UGCC - Papers 1983-01 to 1983-19, F-23-5-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 23-21)
    - UGCC - Papers 1983-20 to 1984-01, 1983 - 1984; F-23-5-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 23-21)
    - UGCC - Papers 1984-02 to 1985-05, 1984 - 1985; F-23-5-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 77-30: Designation of FISC courses for Arts degree, 1977 - 1979; F-23-5-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 77-33: Canadian Studies major, 1977 - 1978; F-23-5-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 77-34: New Course Proposal, Canadian Studies 300-3 Research in Canadian Studies, 1977 - 1978; F-23-5-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-3: New Course Proposal, CMNS 360-3, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-5: New Course Proposal, Canadian Studies 490-5 Graduating Essay, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-6: Double Minor Degree, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-7: Course Proposals, Centre for the Arts, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-8: AME Joint Major Proposal, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-11: Course Proposals, Criminology 460 and 469, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-14: Minor Program in Visual Art, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-15: Practicum Courses in Computing Science, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-17: New Course Proposal Fine and Performing Arts, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-19: Computing Science Calender Changes, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-38.1 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-20: Communication Calendar Changes, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-21: Africa/Middle East Calendar Changes, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-26: Dance Major Proposal, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-29: New Course Proposals, Kinesiology 341 and 441, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 78-30: New Course Proposal, Fine and Performing Arts 334, 1978; F-23-5-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-1: New Course Proposal - General Studies 305-3, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-2: New Course Proposal - General Studies 203-3, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-3: New Course Proposal - Fine and Performing Arts 252, 253, 352, 353, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-4: The Centre for Canadian Studies, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-5: New Course Proposal - Computing Science 393, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-6: New Course Proposal - General Studies 227-3, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79: New Course Proposal - Communications 470-5, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-8: Undergraduate Calendar Changes - Communications, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-9: Revised Course Proposal - Communications 437-5, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-10: Calendar Changes - Latin American Studies, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-11: Calendar Changes - Women's Studies, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-12: Calendar Changes - Canadian Studies, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-13: Calendar Changes - Criminology, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-14: Calendar Changes - Kinesiology, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-15: Calendar Changes - Centre for the Arts, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-16: Calendar Changes - Computing Science, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-17: New Course Proposal - General Studies 350, 351, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-18: New Course Proposal - General Studies 230, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-61 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-19: New Minor Proposal in Museum Education, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-62 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-20: New Program in Systems and Management, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-63 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-21: Bachelor in General Studies Transfer Credit, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-64 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-22: New Course Proposal - Communications 215, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-65 (Archival box - standard 23-22)
    - UGCC - Paper 79-23: New Program - Minor in Music, 1979; F-23-5-1-0-66 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-1: Major in Fine and Performing Arts, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-67 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-2: Re-Offering of General Studies 402-5 and 403-5, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-68 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-3: Sequential Certificate in Criminology, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-69 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-4: Change in Requirements for Certificate in Health and Fitness, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-70 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-5: Credit Hour Change - Canadian Studies 400/401, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-71 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-6: French Canadian Studies Certificate Program - Canadian Studies 390/490, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-72 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-7: Change to Kinesiology Department Core Program, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-73 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-8: Two New Courses in Africa/Middle East, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-74 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-9: Credit Change - Computing Science 103, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-75 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-10 - Canadian Studies Curriculum Changes - French 301/302, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-76 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-11: Canadian Studies Curriculum Changes, 80-11, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-77 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-13: Active Health Science Task Force Report, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-78 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-14: Modification to Africa/Middle East Minor Degree Proposal, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-79 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-15: Computing Science - Digital Systems Design Program, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-80 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-15a: Computing Science Curriculum Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-81 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-16: Criminology - Proposed DISC Programs, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-82 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-17a: Criminology Curriculum Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-83 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-18, 19, 20: Communication Curriculum Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-84 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-21, 21a: Centre for the Arts Curriculum Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-85 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-24: Canadian Studies Curriculum Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-87 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-25: Kinesiology Curriculum Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-88 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-26: Changes in History Courses in Canadian Studies, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-89 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-27: Computing Science Calendar Changes, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-90 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 80-28: Kinesiology Curriculum Changes and Occupational Health Science Program, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-91 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-01: Changes in Degree Regulations - Computing Science, 1980; F-23-5-1-0-92 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-02: Calendar Changes/New Courses - Centre for the Arts, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-93 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-03: New Communication Course Proposal, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-94 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-4 - Curriculum Change - General Studies 106, Opera, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-95 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-5: New Course Proposals - Centre for the Arts, Fine and Performing Arts 152, 162, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-96 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-6: Change in Prerequisite - Women's Studies 301, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-97 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-7: Five Year Plan - Centre for the Arts, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-98 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-9a: Revised Proposal Certificate Program in Communications and Organization, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-99 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-9: Certificate Program - Communications and Organization, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-100 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-10: Joint Listing of Mathematics and Computing Science Courses, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-101 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-11: Computing Science 360 - Course Revision, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-102 (Archival box - standard 23-23)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-12: Proposal for a Diploma Program in Gerontology, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-103 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-14: New Course Proposal - Criminology 411-3, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-104 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-15: New Course Proposal - History 415-3, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-105 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-16: New Course Proposal - Biological Science 444-3, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-106 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-17: New Course Proposal - Kinesiology 460-3 and 461-3, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-107 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-18: Computing Science 101 - New Course Proposal, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-108 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-18: Control of Enrollment in Computing Science, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-109 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-19: General Studies 304 - Credit Change from 5 to 3, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-110 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-21: Computing Science Calendar Changes, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-111 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-22: Centre for the Arts Calendar Changes, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-112 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-23: Curriculum Changes - Criminology, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-113 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-24: Curriculum Changes - Centre for Canadian Studies, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-114 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-25: Curriculum Changes - Centre for the Art, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-115 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-26: Centre for the Arts - Major Program Proposal Visual Art, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-116 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-27: A Study of the Bachelor of General Studies Degree, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-117 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-28: Proposed Change in Procedures for Curriculum Approval, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-118 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-29: Membership Senate Undergraduate Admissions Board, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-119 (Archival box - standard 23-24)